# ZANA KAMAL MOHAMMED

# Mobile and Software Developer

Pirmam-Erbil · +964(750)757 0098

zzanamohammed@yahoo.co.uk · www.linkedin.com/in/zana-mohammed

Experienced Data Assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the retail industry. Skilled in Mobile Application Development, Python (Programming Language), PHP, C++, and Back-End Web Development. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Cihan UNI.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2016 - 2018

#### **SOCIAL MIDEA SPECIALIST, HIWA GAME CENTER**

Managing all social media and related fields such as Designing.

2019

### **MOBILE APPLICATION, HITEXT EXHIBITION**

Freelancer with a register team.

2019 (3 MONTH)

#### **IT MANAGER, SHORSH MARKET 6**

Manages the network and server infrastructure, Maintain Technical Data Reports, Reporting, Troubleshooting, Managing special market system.

2021 (1 MONTH)

#### IT PROJECT MANAGER, DPR

Software proficiency, Data analysis, Cost control, Time management, Problem solving.

2021- PRESENT

#### **DATABASE CLERK, MAJID AL FUTTAIM**

Data processing, Data analysis , Data modeling , Data cleaning, Data visualization , Big data, Attention to detail .

Over all I got a lot of learning courses to be more professional.

## **EDUCATION**

**2016 - 2020 BSC,** CIHAN UNI

## **TECHNICAL (IT) SKILLS**

- Mobile Programming
- Networking
- Web Development (Back-end)
- Robotic
- Data Science
- Database Management (SQL, NonSQL)
- Data Analysis (Python)
- Artificial intelligence
- Software Developing

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Team work
- Flexibility
- Problem Solving
- Self-Management
- Confidence

## **CERTIFICATS**

- ICDL ( Digital Skill For life-Office)
- Data Analysis (edX)
- HITEX
- Typing (Fast typing certificate)
- English Language

## **LANGUAGES**

- Kurdish (Mother language)
- English (Very Good)

- Arabic (Good)
- Persian (Good)

## **PROJECTS**

- Smart House Make a house with all new technology futures, (Bluetooth LED, Sensors, Gas Detector, Fire Detector, Auto LED on off with sun light sensor,...) by using Arduino.
- Feedback System Mobile application it use for giving feedbacks from UNIVERSITY or any education systems, created by Flutter(Dart) and backend with PHP, With MYSQL database.
- **Kurdish Grammar** Mobile application, more useful for 12 grades with search to word ,suggesting a word,.., created by Flutter(Dart) for backend and frontend , with Firebase live database.